Okay,I checked.
我刚看过了
We have Earl Grey,English Breakfast, Cinnamon Stick...
我们有伯爵茶,英式早餐茶,肉桂茶
...Chamomile,Mint Medley, Blackberry and
菊花茶,薄荷茶,黑莓茶
Wait,there's one more. Lemon Soother!
还有…柠檬派
You're not the guy that asked for tea,are you?
你不是那个要喝茶的人对吧?
The One Where The Monkey Gets Away
六人行 第1季 第19集 猴子被送走
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 荣誉出品 河马根据网络字幕微调制作
Mail call! Rachel Greene,bunk seven.
瑞秋,你有信
Thank you.
谢谢
Oh,cool! A free sample of coffee.
酷,免费试喝的咖啡
Oh,good. Because where else would we get any?
太好了,因为在哪儿还有免费的咖啡?
Oh,right.
哦,是啊
-Oh,great. -What is it?
-太好了 -那是什么?
Country club newsletter.
乡村俱乐部的每日公报
My mother sends me the engagement notices for inspiration.
我妈寄来通知有人要订婚了
Oh,my God! It's Barry and Mindy!
噢,我的天!是巴瑞和明蒂
Barry,who you almost
巴瑞,你几乎…
And Mindy,your maid of
明蒂,你的伴娘
Let me see. That's Mindy?
我看看,那是明蒂?
She is pretty!
真漂亮!
Lucky...
她真幸运…
...to have had a friend like you.
有你这样的朋友
Now it's quiet time.
现在是静默时间
Marcel,bring me the rice. Come on.
马修,拿饭给我,快…
Good boy. Give me the rice.
好小子.把饭给我
Thank you. Good boy.
真乖,谢谢
He's mastered the difference between "bring me the" and "pee in the."
他终于能分辨“拿来”和“尿在”的差别了
"Bring me the" and Rach?
瑞秋怎么啦?
Oh,I'm sorry.
抱歉
This is so stupid!
我真是太笨了
I mean,I gave Barry up,right?
是我不要巴瑞的,对吧?
I should be happy for them.
我应该为他们高兴
I am. I'm happy for them.
我…真为他们高兴
-Really? -No.
-真的? -不
I guess it would be different if I were with somebody.
如果我和别人在一起就不同了
Whoa,what....
谁,什么…
What happened to "Forget relationships! I'm done with men!"
你不是说要忘了那段感情,不再和男人在一起
The whole penis embargo?
厌恶男人吗?
I don't know.
我不知道
It's not about no guys. It's about the right guy.
我想这不是没有男人的问题, 而是合适男人的问题
With Barry it was safe and easy, but there was no heat.
和巴瑞在一起安全自在 但是没有激情
With Paolo,all there was,was heat.
和保罗在一起就充满激情
-lt was this raw,animal,sexual -Right. I got it.
-如野兽般原始的性爱 -好了,我懂
I was there.
我看过你们两个在一起的样子
Do you think you can have both?
你认为我能两者同时拥有吗?
Someone who's your best friend but also can make your toes curl.
找到一个能当知己 又能让我感受到激情的人?
Yes.
是呀
Yes,I do. I really do.
我也这么认为.我真的这么认为
In fact,it's funny.
其实说来好笑
Often,someone you wouldn't think could...
时常你认为
...curl your toes...
无法让你感受到激情的人
... might just be the one who...
却是…
...gets interrupted.
被打断了
How was the movie?
电影如何?
-Wonderful! -So good!
-很不错 -很不错
-Suck fest. -Total chick flick.
-逊毙了 -根本是小妞们看的嘛
I'm sorry it wasn't one of those movies with guns and bombs...
真遗撼这不是枪林弹雨
...and buses going really fast!
公车速度奇快的那种电影
I don't need violence in a movie...
暴力并不能吸引我
...as long as there's a little nudity.
只要有裸体镜头我就满足了
-There was nudity. -I meant female nudity.
-那电影也有裸体镜头 -我是指女生的裸体镜头
I don't need to see Lou Grant frolicking.
我不爱看卢葛兰的春宫
Hugh! Hugh Grant!
休葛兰特!
All right,I've got to go.
我得走了
Come on,Marcel.
走吧,马修,快
We're gonna go take a bath. Yes,we are,aren't we?
我们去洗澡,对不对?对
They're still just friends,right?
他们只是朋友吗?
And I will see you tomorrow.
明天见
You're gonna spend tomorrow at Aunt Rachel's.
对,你明天要到瑞秋阿姨家
Does Aunt Monica get a say in this?
等等,摩尼卡阿姨能说句话吗?
Please,Aunt Monica,please?
摩尼卡阿姨请说?
Unclench. You're not even gonna be here.
别紧张了,你不会在这儿的
-I can't believe we're discussing this. -I agree. I'm,like,in disbelief.
-我无法相信我们竟在讨论此事 -我同意,我也无法相信
If it was gonna happen, wouldn't it have happened already?
如果你和瑞秋会爱情产生的话? 还会一直拖到现在吗?
She said she wants a relationship with someone exactly like me.
她说她在寻找像我这样的人
She said that?
她真的这样说?
I added the exactly like me" part.
“像我这样”是我自己加的
But she's looking for someone. And someone will be there tonight.
她说她在寻找某人,而此人今晚就会出现
"Tonight" tonight?
今天晚上?
It's perfect. It'll just be the two of us.
这样最好不过了,因为只有我们两个
She spent all day taking care of my monkey.
她整天都在照顾我的猴子
I can't remember the last time a girl took care of my monkey.
我早已忘记哪个女人照顾过我的猴子
Anyway,I figured after work, I'd pick up some wine...
总之下班后我要去买瓶酒…
...go over there and try to woo her.
去向她“示爱”
Know what you should do?
Know what you should do? 知道你该怎么做吗?
Take her back to the 1 890s when that phrase was last used.
带她回到用“示爱”的十九世纪去
If you keep this up,you'll be finished by the weekend.
如果你继续这样,我发誓这星期内 你就可以和这个浑蛋结束
The one in the feathered boa is Dr. Francis.
围羽毛围巾的是法博土
Now,she used to be a man.
她曾是个男人
Look,there's Raven.
蕾文出现了
We hate her. We're glad she's dying.
我们讨厌她,真高兴她就快死了
And then What? Marcel!
什么?马修!
Are you playing with Monica's shoes? You're not supposed to
想玩摩妮卡的鞋吗?你不能玩…
Marcel,did you poo in the shoe?
马修,你在鞋里大便?
Oh,Marcel! Bad monkey!
天啊,坏猴子
Oh,God!
哦,天哪!
Sorry,Barry.
抱歉,巴瑞
A little engagement gift.
一份小小的订婚礼物
I'm sure you didn't register for that.
我相信你没登记
Who died? Who died?
谁死了?谁死了?
Roll him over! Come on,roll him over!
翻过去!好不好,翻过去!
Well,we know it wasn't Dexter, right,Marcel? Because
好吧,我们知道不是崔斯勒, 因为…马修?…
Marcel?
马修?
-How could you lose him? -I don't know!
-你怎会把它弄丢了呢? -天晓得
We were watching TV, he pooped in Monica's shoe....
我正在看电视, 它在摩妮卡的鞋内大便
Wait. He pooped in my shoe? Which one?
它在我的鞋里大便?哪一双?
I don't know. The left one!
我不知道,左脚
Which ones?
是哪一双?
Those little clunky Amish things you think go with everything.
搭配什么都好看的阿米许鞋
Why is the air in here so negative?
为何一片愁云惨雾?
Rachel lost Marcel.
瑞秋把马修弄丢了
Oh,no! How?
不会吧,怎么丢的?
-He pooped in my shoe. -Which one?
-它在我鞋里大便 -哪只?
The cute black ones I always wear.
我常穿的那只可爱黑鞋
No,which one?
是哪一只?
The right or left?
左脚还右脚?
Because the left one is lucky.
因为左脚是幸运鞋
Come on! What am I gonna do?
大家快想办法!我该怎么办?
All right. You're a monkey. You're loose in the city.
有了,如果你是只猴子,迷失在大城市时
Where do you go?
你会去哪儿?
It's his first time out, so he'll do touristy things.
这是它第一次出门, 所以大概和一般游客一样
I'll go to Cats. You go to the Russian Tea Room.
我去百老汇找.你去俄罗斯茶坊
Oh,my God! Come on,you guys!
别再闹了!
He'll be home any minute. He's gonna kill me!
他马上就会回家,他不会饶过我的
Search the building. Take the first floor. We'll take the rest.
我们从这栋公寓开始找起 你们找一楼和二楼,菲比和我找三楼和四楼
What am I gonna do?
我该怎么办?
You stay here and wait by the phone.
你留在家里等电话
Spray Lysol in my shoe and wait for Ross to kill you.
在我鞋内啧芳香剂,顺便等罗斯回来杀你
Does anybody want to trade?
有人要交换吗?
What do you want?
干嘛?
Mr. Heckles,have you seen a monkey?
哈克先生,我们朋友遗失了一只猴子 你有看见吗?
I left a Belgian waffle out here. Did you take it?
我放了威化饼在这儿,是不是你拿了?
-Why'd you leave it in the hall? -I wasn't ready for it.
-你怎会放威化饼在走廊? -我还不想吃
Have you seen a monkey?
你有看见猴子吗?
I saw Regis Philbin once.
我看过“理吉斯菲邦”
Thank you,Mr. Heckles.
谢谢你,哈克先生
You owe me a waffle.
你们欠我威化饼
He's a black capuchin monkey with a white face...
他是一只白脸的黑卷尾猴
...with Russian dressing and pickles on the side.
加俄国酱外加腌黄瓜
Thanks.
好,谢谢
How did it go today?
今天过得如何?
Oh,great! It went great. Really great.
很好啊!很好啊.真的很不错
Is that wine?
那是酒吗?
You want some?
是的,想喝吗?
Oh,I would love some.
我非常乐意来点
But let's not drink it here.
可是我们别在这儿喝
I'm feeling crazy. You wanna go to Newark?
我感觉有点疯狂,我们去纽华克好吗?
Okay,but before we head off to the murder capital of the Northeast...
前往这东北犯罪首府之前…
... I kind of wanted to run something by you.
…我有些话想说
You know how we were talking before...
我们曾谈过…
...about relationships,and stuff.
…感情的问题
-Oh,God,Ross,I cannot do this! -Okay,quick and painful.
-罗斯,我受不了了! -你回绝得倒是很快嘛
Oh,God!
哦,上帝啊!
Okay,all right. All right,okay.
好吧,好吧
Please don't hate me.
罗斯,别恨我
What?
到底是什么?
You know Marcel?
马修它…
I kind of lost him.
我把它…弄丢了
I can't believe this.
我真不敢相信
All I asked you to do was keep him in here!
我只是麻烦你别让它跑出去
I know. I'm sorry.
我知道,对不起
It's partially my fault.
不,我该负一半的责任
I shouldn't have had you start with a monkey.
我不该叫你照顾猴子
You should have started with a pencil.
应该叫你照顾铅笔才对
I'm doing everything I can. Everyone's looking for him and I got
罗斯,我已尽最大的努力 我已叫大家分头去找
-Who is it? -Animal Control.
-是谁? -动物控制中心
-I've even got Animal Control. -You called Animal Control?
-瞧,我甚至打给动物控制中心 -你打给动物控制中心?
Why? Do you not like them?
怎么了?你不喜欢他们?
Marcel is an illegal exotic animal.
马修是非法的外来动物
I'm not allowed to have him. If they find him,they'll take him away.
我是非法饲养.万一被他们找到他们就会带走它
Well,now,see, you never ever told us that.
好吧,可是,你从来就没有告诉大家
Because I never expected you to invite them to the apartment!
没错,因为我没想到你会请他们来
Thanks for coming.
谢谢你来
Somebody called about a monkey?
有人遗失猴子?
You know,that was a complete misunderstanding.
对,这完全是个误会
We thought we had a monkey, but we didn't.
我以为我们有养猴子, 但是我们没有
-Turned out it was a hat. -Cat!
-结果是帽子 -猫!
We checked,no one's seen Marcel.
我们查过了,没人看到马修
-My uncle Marcel. -ls that who the monkey's named after?
-我叔叔马修 -那猴子是以你叔叔命名?
Possession of an illegal exotic is punishable...
你知道持有非法外来动物
... by two years in prison and confiscation of the animal.
可判刑两年并没收动物?
Oh,my God!
天啊
You'd put that poor little creature in jail?
你要把这可怜的小东西关进监牢?
Remember how we talked about saying things quietly to yourself first?
菲比,你记得如何先对自己小声说吗?
Yes,but there isn't always time.
记得,但总不是时候
I'm sure there's some friendly way to reconcile this. Have a seat.
我相信我们能以友善的处理方式,请坐
We haven't met. I'm Monica Geller.
首先,我们还没自己介绍,我叫摩妮卡
Oh,my God,you are!
天啊,你是莫尼卡
And you're Rachel Greene!
还有,你是瑞秋对吗?
Luisa Gianetti! Lincoln High?
露莎,林肯高中
I sat behind you guys in homeroom.
我坐在你们后面
Luisa! Oh,my God!
露莎!哦,天哪!
Monica! It's Luisa!
摩妮卡,是露莎
I went there too!
我也去了那里!
Luisa! From homeroom!
是在后面那个?
You have no idea who I am,do you?
你们根本不知道我是谁对不?
-No. -Not at all.
-不 -一点也不
Well,maybe that's because you spent four years ignoring me.
或许你们那四年,都在当我不存在
Would it have been hard to say, "Morning,Luisa"...
难道说“早安,露莎”
...or "Nice overalls"?
或“好漂亮的连身裤”有那么困难吗?
Oh,I'm so sorry!
对不起
It's not so much you. You were fat. You had your own problems.
我不怪你,你当时很胖, 你有自己的烦恼
But you. What a bitch!
可是你实在是个贱货
What?
什么?
You know what? Be that as it may...
别计较了
...could you help us with the monkey thing,for old times'sake?
你真认为你能帮我们找猴子? 看在过去的份上?
Go,Bobcats!
帮我们找
I could. But I won't.
我可以,我不
If I find that monkey,he's mine.
如果我找到猴子,它就是我的了
Sorry.
抱歉
Marcel?
马修?
Hi,can I help you?
需要帮忙吗?
We're having an emergency, and we were looking for something.
我们有急事,我们在找东西
-A monkey. -Yes,have you seen any?
-猴子 -对,你有看见吗?
No,I haven't seen a monkey.
我没看见猴子
Can you fix radiators?
你知道如何修理散热器吗?
Sure! Did you try turning the knob back the other way?
当然!你试过将转钮转回去吗?
-Of course! -Oh. Then,no.
-当然! -那之后我就不知道了
-Taste this. Is there too much rum? -Just a second.
-试试这个是不是加太多兰姆酒了? -等等
-Hope you find your monkey. -No,wait!
-希望你们能找到猴子 -不,等等
We may not know about radiators...
我们对散热器或许不太懂
... but we do have expertise in the heating and cooling milieu.
我们可是冷暖环境的专家
Aren't we in the middle of something?
我们不是正在忙吗?
But these women are very hot, and they need our help.
对,她们很热而且需要帮助
And they're very hot!
而且很火辣
We can't,all right?
我们不行
We're sorry.
抱歉你们不知道
You don't know how sorry. We promised to find this monkey.
我们有多抱歉,我们答应人家要找猴子
He's this high and answers to the name Marcel.
它约这么高,名叫马修
So if we could get pictures of you, it'd help us out.
如果能拥有你们的照片,就算是帮了大忙
From now on,you don't get to talk to other people.
从现在起不准你和其他人讲话
-Oh,my God! -What?
-噢,我的天! -什么?
Something brushed up against my right leg.
有东西碰到我的右脚
Oh,it's okay. It was just my left leg.
没什么,是我的左脚
Look,Phoebe!
看,菲比
Oh,Marcel! Come here!
马修,过来…
Step aside,ladies.
站过去,两位小姐
-What are you gonna do? -Just a tranquilizer.
-你要干什么? -打镇定剂
Run,Marcel,run!
快跑,马修,快跑!
Damn!
坏了!
-Are you okay? -I think so.
-你还好吧? -还行.哦
Oh,gosh!
哦，糟了!
We've been all over the neighborhood! He's just gone!
我们把周围的邻居都找遍了, 它不见了,就这么消失了
-You don't know that. -It's cold,it's dark.
-罗斯,还不一定 -拜托,天气好冷天又黑
He doesn't know the Village!
它根本不认识路!
And now I have a broken foot. I have no monkey and a broken foot!
现在我的脚又受伤了, 猴子没了还换来受伤的脚
Thank you very much!
真的感谢你!
I've said I'm sorry a million times.
罗斯,我已向你道歉过无数次
What do you want me to do?
你到底要我怎么样?
You want me to break my foot too? I'll break it right now.
你也要我的脚受伤?要我也把脚弄伤
Oh,my God! There,are you happy now?
瞧,高兴了吧
Yeah,now that you kicked the sign...
对,你踢完路标后
... I don't miss Marcel anymore!
我突然不再想念马修了
It's not like I did this on purpose.
我真的不是故意的
No,this is just vintage Rachel.
当然,这是典型的瑞秋
Things just sort of happen around you!
这种事常发生在你身上
You're off in "Rachel Land," doing your "Rachel Thing"...
你活在自己的世界中 做着自己的事情…
...oblivious to people's monkeys or to people's feelings and
完全无视别人的猴子, 或是别人的感觉…
I don't want to hear it! Forget it,okay?
罗斯,我不想听!忘了他,好不好?
What?
什么?
Hey,banana man!
嗨,香蕉男!
This is so intense!
这下可好
One side of my butt is totally asleep and the other side has no idea.
一边的屁股在睡觉, 另一边却毫无所知
-What's with Phoebe? -Tranquilizer dart.
-菲比怎么啦? -麻醉枪
Hi! Did you order some bananas?
你有订香蕉吗?
-What about it? -Give me my monkey back!
-那是干吗的? -还我的猴子
-I don't have a monkey. -Then what's with the bananas?
-我没猴子 -干嘛买一箱香蕉?
Potassium.
补充钾
Okay,where is he?
马修?它在哪儿?
You're wasting your time.
你在浪费时间
What?
什么?
-What have you done to him? -That's my monkey. That's Patty.
-你对他干了什么? -这是我的猴子,它叫佩蒂
Are you insane? Come here,Marcel.
你疯了不成?过来,马修…
Come here,Patty.
过来,佩蒂
Come here,Marcel.
过来,马修…
Come here,Patty.
过来,佩蒂
Here,monkey.
猴子过来…
Here,monkey!
过来,猴子!
Gotcha!
总算逮到你了
-Give me my monkey back! -It's mine.
-把我的猴子还给我 -那是我的猴子
Take this up with the judge.
你们到法官面前去争吧
That's not my monkey. The dress is mine. Send it back whenever.
那不是我的猴子 只有衣服是我的,随时可以送回来
All right,I want my monkey!
好吧,我要我的猴子!
-Oh,come on,Luisa. -Sorry,prom queen.
-露莎,拜托 -抱歉了,舞会皇后
You had to be a bitch in school, instead of fat.
你高中时干嘛那么贱,为何不当个胖妹?
In high school,I was prom queen...
在学校我是舞会皇后
...and the homecoming queen and you...
返校皇后,但是你
...were also there.
你也在的啊
But this isn't high school. We're all adults here!
但是这不是高中,我们现在都是成年人!
Heckles! Can I have this?
我能要这个吗?
For the most part.
随意
If you take this monkey,I'll lose an important person in my life.
如果你把猴子带走 我将失去我生命中重要的人
You can hate me if you want, but please do not punish him.
你可以恨我,请别折磨他
You have a chance to be the bigger person here.
此时你有机会成为大人物
Take it!
把握机会吧
No.
不
All right. Then I'll call your supervisor and tell her...
那么,我只好告诉你的长官
...you shot my friend with a dart!
你在我朋友的屁股上开了一枪
It'll be nice to get this off, won't it?
终于能脱去这件衣服,不是吗?
Or we can leave it on. That's fine.
或是这样也不错
With the right pumps, that would be a great little outfit.
配上鞋就是完整的一套
Listen,I'm sorry I was so hard on you before
抱歉,我对你这么凶
No,it was my fault. I almost lost your
不,这都是我的错,我差点…
Yeah,but you got him back. You were great.
不,它也是你找回来的,你做得很好
We still have that bottle of wine.
那瓶酒还在
Are you in the mood for something grape?
有心情喝杯葡萄酒吗?
-Sure,that would be good. -All right.
-好呀 -很好
The neighbors must be vacuuming.
隔壁一定在用吸尘器
Well,as long as we're here...
只要我们在这儿…
...and not on the subject....
…不谈那个话题…
I was thinking about...
我在想…
... how mad we got at each other before.
…我们刚刚实在是恶言相向
And maybe it was partially because of how we
大概是因为我们…
-Rachel? -Barry?
-瑞秋? -瑞秋?
I can't do it. I can't marry Mindy.
我办不到.我无法和明蒂结婚
I think I'm still in love with you.
我想我爱的人依然是你
We have got to start locking that door!
我们得开始锁门了!
Show us! Come on!
给我们看看!来吗!
-lt was such a long time ago. -Okay,fine. All right.
-很久很久以前 -好吧
This is me in The Sound of Music. See the von Trapp kids?
这是我在“音乐之声”里面, 看见范崔普的孩子吗?
That's because I'm in front of them.
因为我挡在他们前面
Big nun!
大修女!
I thought that was an alp.
我以为那是阿尔卑斯山
High school wasn't my favorite time.
我的高中时代并不如意
I loved high school.
我爱高中
It was four years of parties, dating and sex and
四年的舞会,约会和做爱
Well,I went to boarding school with 400 boys.
我和400个男孩上的住宿学校
Any sex I had would've involved a major lifestyle choice.
每次做爱都是一次生活方式的重大抉择
Doesn't it seem like a million years ago?
天啊,那不是回到史前时代?
My butt cheek is waking up!
我的屁股醒了